Guide to the Richard W. Lyman Personal Papers SC0562
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1990-110
  - Speeches and Speech Materials
    - Stanford University Commencement speech (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, speech, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Associated Colleges of New England, informal speech at Wellesley, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Symposium "Philanthropy in the Reagan Years," CUNY, May 4, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Farewell occasions at Rockefeller Foundation, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Symposium "Understanding Evil," Institute for the Humanities, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - R. F. Board presentation on domestic programs, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - R. F. Board presentation on domestic programs, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Atlanta University Center speech, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - TARGET SEATTLE talk, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - University of Texas Austin, Centennial celebration, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - AAFRC talk, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - ACLS talk, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - ACLS, 1985: papers (1) (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - ACLS, 1985: papers (2) (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - ACLS, 1985: papers (3) (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Columbia University Seminars dinner, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Conference of Southwest foundations, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous speeches (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Coalition of College Presidents for Civic Responsibility, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Stanford University, speech to Fellows, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - National Guild of Community Schools of the Arts, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - NSFRE, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wider Opportunities for Women, 20th anniversary, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Citron taping, 1982 (1) (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Citron taping, 1982 (2) (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - AAHE keynotes, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - UVM commencement, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - WPI commencement, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - AAAS annual meeting, 1982 (1) (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - AAAS annual meeting, 1982 (2) (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - American Educational Research Association talk, 1982 (1) (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - American Educational Research Association talk, 1982 (2) (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Stanford Univ. 93rd commencement address, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - American Association of Museums, keynote, 1981 (1) (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - American Association of Museums, keynote, 1981 (2) (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Fourth Congress of Inter-American Organization for Higher Education, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Corporate education (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Albany, NY, museum talk, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Thacher School, commencement address, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Shands Lecture, Stanford University, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Stanford University miscellaneous (1) (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Stanford University miscellaneous (2) (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Stanford University miscellaneous (3) (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Stanford University miscellaneous (4) (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Stanford University miscellaneous (5) (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Stanford University miscellaneous (6) (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Students' Papers
    - Student papers: A-D (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Student papers: G-J (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Student papers: M-Pa (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Student papers: Po-Z (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers
    - "Gownsmen Daily News," May 11, 1926 (Box 30 os, Folder 1)
    - The British Worker, May 11, 1926 (Box 30 os, Folder 2)
    - Western Vindicator, Dec. 14, 1839 [Chartists publication] (Box 30 os, Folder 3)
    - British election and political posters, ca. 1910 (Box 30 os, Folder 4)
    - Lithograph portrait of George Canning, n.d. (Box 30 os, Folder 5)
    - Maps of British isles, 1778-1860; map of German/Austria, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Newspapers from England, 1959-60 (Box 31 os)
    - Newspapers from England, 1959-65 (Box 32 os)
    - Newspapers from England, 1952-65 (Box 33 os)
    - Newspapers from England, 1963 (Box 34 os)
  - Correspondence
    - Letter to "Pete" from "Dad"; letterhead reads "Willy Pogany," n.d. [found in original box from England] (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: A (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: B (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: B (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: C (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: C (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: D (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: E (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: F (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: G (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: H (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: H (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: I-J (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: K (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: L (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: M (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: M (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: M (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: N (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: O-P (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: P (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: R (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: S (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: S (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: S (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: T (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: U-V (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: W (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: W (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence re: Rockefeller Foundation presidency, 1980: X-Z (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Christmas cards and letters, 1984 (Box 38)
    - Christmas cards and letters, 1985 (Box 39)
    - Christmas cards and letters, 1986 (Box 40)
    - Christmas cards and letters, 1987 (Box 41)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1991-135
  - Correspondence Files
    - APC – Action plans for Change (Robert Street - SUL) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - APC – Action plans for Change (Robert Street - SUL) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - American Assembly Nov. 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - American Association of Higher Education (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - American Historical Association (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report – Financial History (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Annual Financial Report 1990 (includes "The Management of International Relations at Stanford University – As Compared with the Universities of Berlin (West)" by Hannelore Hegel, 1988) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Carnegie Corporation of New York (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Centennial International Symposium (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Centennial Symposium 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Centennial – San Diego: Dec. 1, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Centennial: Orange County (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Center for the Study of Philanthropy, 1988-91 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Columbia University – Philanthropy: Francis X. Sutton, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Academic Appraisal (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Council on International Education Exchange (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Defense Language Institute, 1988-89 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Freshman Advising Program (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Fundamental Standards, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Finn vs. Stanford (RWL declaration), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Management Development Program (MDP) (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Martin Luther King Fund Letter, 1988-89 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - National Humanities Alliance, 1988-90 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - North American Conference on British Studies, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Public Affairs Repositioning, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Stanford University, miscellaneous, 1988-90 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - VTSS (Values, Technology, Science, and Society): Barry Katz, 1988-90 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1985-91 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1998-166
  - Asilomar May 1-3, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - IBM proxy (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Washington Center Board, 1988-1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, out, drafts, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, out, drafts, 1990 (1 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, out, drafts, 1990 (2 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, out, drafts, 1990 (3 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, out, drafts, 1990 (4 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, out, mostly drafts, Sept. 1989 - Jan. 1990 (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, out, mostly drafts, Sept. 1989 - Jan. 1990 (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, out, drafts, May - Aug. 1989 (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, out, drafts, May - Aug. 1989 (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, out, drafts, Nov. 1988 - Apr. 1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - R. W. Lyman Award Ceremony, Nov. 30, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - End of an Era, Nov. 29, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - AASCU, Fairmount Hotel Nov. 21, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Continuing Education (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Aid to Artisans Board, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Aid to Artisans Board, 1988-89 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Association I (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Association II (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Association III (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - R.C. Smart, "Background to Inflation in Britain, 1880-1975" with cover letter to Lyman, July 11, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association IV (1993-1995) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - World Management Council (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - CIV: background documents (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - CIV: chron file I (Oct. 1995 - Oct. 1996) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - CIV: chron file II (Oct. 1996 - Jan. 1997) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - CIV: chron file III (Jan. - May 1997) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Yale University Accreditation Nov. 16, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Yale University NEASC Self-Study Report (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Yale University Accreditation (1) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Yale University Accreditation (2) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Yale University Accreditation (3) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Yale University Accreditation - report (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Accountability of Colleges & Universities: A Study [1995-96] - reimbursements (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Accountability of Colleges & Universities: A Study [1995-96] - correspondence (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Accountability of Colleges & Universities: A Study [1995-96] - correspondence among the four (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Accountability of Colleges & Universities: A Study [1995-96] - interviews and notes (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Accountability of Colleges & Universities: A Study [1995-96] - Jan. 14, 1995 meeting (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Accountability of Colleges & Universities: A Study [1995-96] - Boston / D.C. trip (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Accountability of Colleges & Universities: A Study [1995-96] - New York City meeting July 1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Accountability of Colleges & Universities: A Study [1995-96] - San Francisco August 1995 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Accountability of Colleges & Universities: A Study [1995-96] - Beginnings (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Accountability of Colleges & Universities: A Study [1995-96] - Background materials (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Accountability of Colleges & Universities: A Study [1995-96] - Drafts (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Accountability of Colleges & Universities: A Study [1995-96] - Published essay 1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Lyman's desk diaries 1988-1990 [4 volumes] (Box 3, Folder 40608)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges. Commission on the Academic Presidencey [AGB-CAP] 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - AGB-CAP 2 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - AGB-CAP 3 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - AGB-CAP Washington, DC, Jan. 20 - Feb 5, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - AGB-CAP briefing book (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - AGB miscellaneous papers (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - AGB financial reports (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - AGB Board of Directors meeting packets (agenda, reports, etc.) 1994 - Jan. 1995 (Box 3, Folder 14-17)
  - AGB Board of Directors meeting packets (agenda, reports, etc.) Mar. 1995 - Nov. 1997 (Box 4)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2003-026
  - Correspondence, memoranda, proposals and reports from the National Center for Postsecondary Improvement, 1996- 2000 (Box 1)
  - Questionnaires and other materials related to UCMI work, 1988 (Box 1)
  - "Study of the Stanford Faculty" by Bradley Efron, Aug. 25, 1972 (Box 1)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2003-079
  - Photograph with Rockefeller Trustees (Box 4)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2008-319
  - Source materials & drafts of his book Stanford in Turmoil: Campus Unrest, 1966-1972
    - Accountability – M. Trow writings (Box 1)
    - Accountability – published materials (Box 1)
    - Interpretations of the Movement, Student Power, etc. (Box 1)
    - The Book (mostly on various collections of use) (Box 1)
    - HBF [H. Bruce Franklin] (Box 1)
    - Lew Spitz items (Box 1)
    - Drafts of chapters (Box 1)
    - [2 misc. items] (Box 1)
    - [mostly copied sources (Box 1)
    - Loose: paper-clipped bunches of photocopied source material from S. U. Archives (Box 1)
    - Original clippings 1968 (Box 2)
    - S.U. News Service – press releases 1968-69 (Box 2)
    - Evan Nordby's honors thesis "Fire and Sandstone: Anti-Vietnam War Activism at Stanford, 1966-1970" 2000 (Box 2)
    - Assorted sources (Box 2)
    - Chapter drafts (Box 2)
    - Wascher, James D. "Academic Freedom and the Campus Revolution: The Dismissal of H. Bruce Franklin," Senior Research Project, Northwestern University School of Law, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Notecards and notes (Box 2)
    - Fischer, Wolfram "The Student Revolt in Germany and Its Impact" – paper for seminar at CASBS, Stanford, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Report of the Special Committee on Campus Tensions, Sol M. Linowitz, Chairman [3 versions] 1970 (Box 2)
    - John W. Chapman, 2 papers (Box 2)
    - General Interpretations (Box 2)
    - Black Student Union – RWL summary of 1968 and some source materials (Box 2)
    - Text of Franklin Statement (newsprint) (Box 2)
    - Loose: assorted publications re student unrest at other colleges and in general (Box 2)
    - Photocopied source materials from S. U. Archives (Box 2)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2014-099
  - Correspondence
    - Algard, Anne, 2008-2011 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, Alun, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - A, 1987-2006 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Baker, Russell, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Bacchetti, Raymond F., 1988-2009 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Barr, Bernadine, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Basch, Paul, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Bechtel, Riley, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Bechtel, Stephen, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Belton, Erline, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Berlin, Isaiah, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Berstein. Thomas P., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Beyers, Robert W, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Bing, Peter, 1989-1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Bok, Derek, 1990-2006 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Bowen, William G, 1992-2010 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Brewer, Betsy, 1988-2001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Brokaw, Tom, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Brown, John (President: Coe College), 1988-2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Brynn, Edward (1/2), 2002-2006 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Brynn Edward (2/2), 1996-2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Buchanan, Peter McE., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - B (1/4), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - B (2/4), 1992-2004 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - B (3/4), 2005-2010 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - B (4/4), 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Carnochan, 1990-2005 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Casper, Gerhard II (1/2), 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Casper, Gerhard (2/2), 1993-2000 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Castro, Joseph I., 1994-2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Cicero, Linda (1/2), 2011 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Cicero, Linda A (2/2), 2010 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Chance, William M., 1989-2009 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Clark, Burton R, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Choi, Steven, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Clausen, A. W. (Tom), 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Clinton, C.A (1/2), 1996-2007 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Clinton, C.A (2/2), 1991-2005 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Andreotti, Meguid Woo, 1989-1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Conley, Frances, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Craig, Gordon A, 2000-2007 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Crawford, Sir Fred, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Cuban, Larry, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cugell, David W, 2002-2011 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - C (1/2), 1989-2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - C (2/2), 1992-2006 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - David, Janet, 2002-2011 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - De Mesquita, Bruce Bueno, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Diamond, Larry, 1990-1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Drell, Sid, 1988-2006 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Duggan, Susan J. (1/2), 2004-2011 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Duggan, Susan J. (2/2), 1992-2007 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - D, 1988-2010 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Earle, Gordon, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Edmundson, Kathryn L, 1991-2008 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Edwards, Robert H., 1995-2001 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Ellsworth, Gretchen G, 1988-2011 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Eshoo, Anna, 1993-2009 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Etchemendy, John, 2000-2004 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - E, 1989-2010 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Fagen, Richard, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Falcon, Wally, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Feinstein, Dianne, 1993-2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Fetter, Jean H., 1992-1997 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Fleishman, Joel, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Franklin, Patricia, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Frederickson, George, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Fuchs, Victor, 1994-2007 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Fuller, Anina Porter, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Fusco, Gregory, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - F, 1988-2010 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Gamson, David, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Gardner John W., 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Guadiani, Claire, 1990-1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Gallagher, M & Shapiro R., 1997-2003 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Gardner, John W., 1991-2002 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Gilbert, Martin, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Gilbert, Parker, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Gill, Brendan, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Gildred, Ted, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Goldman, Merle (1/2), 1990-2005 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Goldman, Merle (2/2), 1996-2011 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Gombrich, Ernst & Ilse, 1996-2009 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Gomery, Ralph E., 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Graham, Hugh D, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Gregg, Bob, 1992-2009 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Gumport, Patricia J., 1994-2006 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Gunther, Gerald, 1979-2002 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - G (1/2), 1979-1999 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - G (2/2), 2002-2011 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Hamilton, Edward K., 1994-2005 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Hastorf, Albert H, 1997-2011 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Harte, Chris, 1999-2003 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Hauptman, Arthur, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Heller, Tom, 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Henderson, Andrea, 2007-2009 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Hennessey, John, 2000-2009 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Hester, Ralph, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Hexter, 1993-2000 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Hexter, J.H., 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Henderson, Andrea D., 2008 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Hills, Reuben and Ingrid, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Holmgren, Bob, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Horton, Larry, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Huang, Peter, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Huntington, Nancy, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Husaini, S. Wager Award, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Huxley, Carole, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - H (1/3), 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - H (2/3), 1994-2002 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - H (3/3), 1982-2010 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - I, 1990-2005 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - James, Cheewa, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - J, 1991-2009 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Kaiser, Herb & Joy, 1998-2011 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Katchadourian, Herant & Stina, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Keal, Paul, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Kaufman, Kenneth C., 1991-2007 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Kelley, Ryland & Shirley, 1990-2011 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Kenneth, David, 1993-2011 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kennedy, Donald, 1988-2007 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Keohane, Nannerl O., 1991-2006 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Kimball, Maggie, 1997-2011 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Kirst, Mike, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Knapp, Burke, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Kollman, Jack, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - K, 1988-2010 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Lambert, Richard D, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Lane, L.W., 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Lardner, Olatunji, 1989-1993 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Lavine, Steven D, 1994-2002 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Lewis, John, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Levin, Henry, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Lho, Kyongsoo Kevin, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Li, Dr. K. T., 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Li, Victor, 1989-2002 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Lieberman, Gerald J, 1995-2005 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Lord, Joseida, 1996-1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Lowenthal, Abe, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Luftglass, Rick, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Mc Cone, John, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - McLaughlin, Judith Block, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - McNeill, J. Ian, 1993-2002 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Mancall, Mark, 2002-2007 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Marting, Leeda, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Massy, William F, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Mathiopoulos, Margarita, 1994-2001 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Maxwell, David & Mandy, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - May, Andrew, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - McCulloch, Sam, 1991-1996 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Milliken, Christine T., 1995-2008 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Minott, Rodney, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Montgomery, Parker, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Morita, Akio (Sony Corp.), 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Murray, James J., 1994 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Moock, Joyce L., 1992-2007 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Mushatt, Ann, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - M, 1991-2011 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Newman, Frank, 1999-2004 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - N, 1988-2011 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Oberman, Ida (1/3), 1995-2011 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Oberman, Ida (2/3), 1997-2007 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Oberman, Ida (3/3), 2004-2010 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - O'Connell, Brian, 1990-2011 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - O, 1988-2009 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Packer, George, 1973-2005 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Padulo, Louis, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Patterson, Jayne, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Peeps, 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Perry, William, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Pope, Norris, 2007-2011 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Post, Gaines Jr., 1989-2009 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Rosborough, Brian A, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 10)